[tense music playing]
[narrator] The Hunters
have entered the palace
in order to exterminate
the Chimera Ant King.
I guess my attacks
don't affect it at all.
What is that damn thing?
[chuckles]
Don't run away! Answer me!
What is this?
[narrator] To spare the injured Shoot
and to draw
Youpi's attention to himself,
Knuckle began
to taunt him mercilessly.
[dramatic music playing]
[roaring]
[Meleoron] Damn!
Knuckle's planning to fight Youpi alone,
and I can't get to him,
not through that deadly,
sword-like onslaught.
There's no way!
In that case…
[Shoot] No. I can't pass out,
not now.
If I do,
[groans]
…still keep going.
[Meleoron] Right now,
my job isn't to help him.
[sobs]
No matter how much I want to!
My job is to use my power
to help the others
to complete the mission
as fast as possible.
[narrator] Though it broke his heart,
Meanwhile, Ikalgo proceeded
further into the palace
[Ikalgo] Satellite Dragonflies.
Any friend of theirs
is a friend of mine.
[narrator] Morel was first
to reach the throne room,
and he waited to continue
his battle with Pouf,
Gon and Killua
located their target, Neferpitou,
all for the purpose
of avenging their friend, Kite.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
REVENGE X AND X RECOVERY
Do you…
remember who I am?
And I came here for one reason,
to make you restore Kite!
Pitou's defenseless,
might as well be completely naked.
Does Pitou think we're beatable…
without using aura?
Nobody can fight that naked,
not even Pitou.
But if that's the case,
why doesn't it look that way?
[suspenseful music playing]
It almost looks like…
That's it!
protecting the weak from a predator.
But that's ridiculous.
No way Pitou's capable of that.
[Killua] Why was he so cryptic?
[gasps]
conjuring images in his mind
of his broken friend, Kite.
[rattling]
so come and fight me!
[gasps]
[panting]
Get up! We're going outside!
[narrator] Gon needed
an outlet for his rage,
but with Pitou being
so unexpectedly submissive,
he had none.
Meanwhile, Killua was
starting to understand
what was going on. It was…
[Zeno] I know nothing
beyond the mission I was given.
his mission was probably to use
Dragon Dive and Dragon Head
to get the King and his Royal Guards
away from each other,
Pitou's healing her
on the King's orders.
when it's being used.
[narrator] But as important
as this information was,
[Killua] What do I do?
What should I say?
-Gon!
-I'll do anything!
[Neferpitou gasps]
I'll do anything
you want me to do,
but you have to wait, because I…
[gasps]
[narrator] Pitou didn't know
what to say in this situation,
[narrator] The truth,
plain and simple.
[Neferpitou] Because of her,
the King became who he is today.
If she ceases to exist, the King
will cease to be who he is.
I beg you to let me heal her,
and then I'll do
anything you ask of me,
so please just wait.
[Gon] You want to save her life?
You're telling me that you really…
want to save this girl's life?
[Gon shuddering]
How dare you… say that?
Damn it! Why, you…
probably because of us…
and Grandpa's Dragon Dive.
[Gon] And?
[Killua] And Pitou's likely healing her.
Well, that's what it looks like, anyway.
[Gon] So?
Hold off.
Wait until it's done.
[Gon] "Likely"? "Probably"?
"Probably"? "Likely"?
For real?
The hell with that!
Quit messing around!
[Gon panting]
[shouts] What the hell's
the matter with you?
Because there's no way in hell!
[arm cracks]
[both gasp]
[dramatic music playing]
[angelic choir singing]
[Neferpitou] If you like,
I'll break my right arm as well,
and if that's not enough…
then I'll break my legs.
[Neferpitou whimpers]
If you truly think that
I won't keep my promise
after I heal her,
you can mangle my body
all you want,
as long as it doesn't
hinder my ability to treat her.
[chorus continues]
[grunts]
[shuddering]
[shudders]
I want you to tell me!
[gasps]
[Gon] Show me--
[Killua] No. You kill Pitou,
Must be real nice for you.
I'm only saying this,
because it looks like you're losing it.
Did you forget what you told me
in the very beginning?
We're here to get Kite back.
Get it together, damn it!
Okay.
I've calmed down now.
For how long?
How long should we wait?
[gasps]
Uh, I estimate it will take
three to four hours
to heal her completely.
I'll wait right here for one hour.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Killua] I kind of feel better now.